<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sponsors on My New Hugo Site</title><link>/sponsors/</link><description>Recent content in Sponsors on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/sponsors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alaska Division of Mining, Land and Water</title><link>/sponsors/ak-dmlw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sponsors/ak-dmlw/</guid><description>you can find Alaska Division of mining, Land and Water website here</description></item><item><title>FBI</title><link>/sponsors/fbi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sponsors/fbi/</guid><description>you can find FBI&amp;rsquo;s website here</description></item><item><title>Firstline</title><link>/sponsors/firstline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sponsors/firstline/</guid><description>Experience &amp;amp; Leadership Since 1987, Firstline has grown into the Northwest’s leading provider of Voice and IT services for small to large enterprises.
Based in Bellevue, WA, we serve thousands of clients and their local and global locations. Our partnerships and resources enable us to serve client locations in markets across America and the world.
We serve every industry and business model, including Hospitality, Healthcare, Tech, Software, Financial Services, Retail, Government/Education, and Real Estate.</description></item><item><title>MTA</title><link>/sponsors/mta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sponsors/mta/</guid><description>MTA is the leading broadband technology company empowering its member-owners to live a connected life. MTA will continue to pioneer economic development providing the infrastructure necessary for its communities to thrive and grow together well into the future.
you can find MTA&amp;rsquo;s website here</description></item><item><title>Northriver IT</title><link>/sponsors/northriverit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sponsors/northriverit/</guid><description>Since 2004, Northriver IT has been called coach, A-team, reinforcements. With premium solutions and personalized service; choose Northriver IT. Wise people, wise move.
you can find Northriver IT&amp;rsquo;s website here</description></item><item><title>Structured</title><link>/sponsors/structured/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sponsors/structured/</guid><description>Structured is an award-winning solution provider delivering secure, cloud-connected digital infrastructure. For nearly 30 years, we’ve helped clients through all phases of digital transformation by securely bridging people, business and technology. Customers trust us to provide valuable insight throughout the process of selecting and implementing secure and scalable IT strategies, platforms, and processes that meet modern expectations and drive measurable improvements throughout the enterprise.
Today’s connected economy utilizes technology much differently than it did a decade ago, driving change in how organizations interact with employees and clients.</description></item></channel></rss>